[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The human laryngeal prominence got its common name from this biblical figure.", "correct_answer": "Adam", "incorrect_answers": ["Jacob", "Abraham", "Joseph"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In P.T. Andersons There Will Be Blood, which one of the Sunday Family tells Daniel about the oil?", "correct_answer": "Paul", "incorrect_answers": ["Mary", "Eli", "Abel"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The U.S. state of Oregon has been nicknamed after this animal, which is the official state animal.", "correct_answer": "Beaver", "incorrect_answers": ["Raccoon", "Marmot", "Bear"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why do two patients sometimes have appointments with the same doctor at the same time?", "correct_answer": "Because of no-shows", "incorrect_answers": ["Because the doctors time is more valuable than the patients time", "Usually due to a scheduling error", "To make the patients angry"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many of the Top 10 American films of all time (as chosen by the American Film Institute), did NOT win an Oscar for Best Picture?", "correct_answer": "Four", "incorrect_answers": ["None. They all won the Best Picture Award.", "All 10", "Five"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who created the character of James Bond?", "correct_answer": "Ian Fleming", "incorrect_answers": ["Alistair McLean", "George Sand", "Louis Bromfield"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which term refers to the number of complete cycles of an alternating current that occur per second?", "correct_answer": "Frequency", "incorrect_answers": ["Watt", "Wavelength", "Ohm"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Author Dean Koontz was so upset with the 1996 film version of this book that he has demanded creative control over every film based on one of his books.", "correct_answer": "Hideaway", "incorrect_answers": ["Watchers", "Carrie", "Phantoms"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the capital and largest city of Lebanon?", "correct_answer": "Beirut", "incorrect_answers": ["Bujumbura", "Dhaka", "Baghdad"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This term is commonly used to refer to a person who becomes overly upset or angry when confronted with an issue.", "correct_answer": "defensive", "incorrect_answers": ["repressed", "caustic", "sublime"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do you call an Austrian dessert that is a sweet almond paste dipped in chocolate?", "correct_answer": "Marzipan", "incorrect_answers": ["Apfelstrudel", "Hei\u00dfe Schokolade", "Sachertorte"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "I came here tonight because when you realize you want to spend the rest of your life with somebody, you want the rest of your life to start as soon as possible. (1989)", "correct_answer": "When Harry Met Sally", "incorrect_answers": ["Wuthering Heights", "Youve Got Mail", "The Mask of Zorro"]}]